Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Committees, 1944-1989
  - Committee on 'How to Conduct an Effective Strike in An Automated Industry', 1972 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Structural Review Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Structural Review Committee, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Structural Review Committee, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Future, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Quality of Work Life: Agreement between CWA and Michael Maccoby for Consulting Services, 1982-1986 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Technology and Competition Conference, April 19, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Management Committee: Wage Rate for New Job-Coupon Sales Representative, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Blue Ribbon Committee on Jurisdiction, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Merger Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Quality of Work Life: Resource Bulletins, 1982-1986 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Quality of Work Life: Leaders' Guide, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life: CWA and Staff Unions, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Quality of Work Life: Conference Annoucements, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Quality of Work Life: Journals, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Speeches: Michael Maccoby, "Management and Leadership", 1980 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Committee to Review and Establish Procedures for Ratification, 1966-1967 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-District One, 1964-1969 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-Districts Two and Three, 1966-1969 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-District Four, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-District Five, 1966-1969 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-District Six, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-Districts Seven, Eight and Nine, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Ratification Study Committee-Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Presentation and Ratification Study Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Presentation and Ratification Study Committee-Final Reports, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Bargaining Committee: Contract Presentation and Ratification Study Committee-Final Reports, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Bargaining Committee: Reactivated Contract Presentation and Ratification Study Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Concerned Women Advancement Committee, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Committee: Business Service Representatives Report, 1980-1981 (Box 58A, Folder 1)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Committee: General Corr., 1980-1981 (Box 58A, Folder 2)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Committee: Report, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 3)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Committee: Clerk, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 4)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Plan, 1982-1985 (Box 58A, Folder 5)
  - Occupational Job Evaluation Committee: Research, 1987-1988 (Box 58A, Folder 6)
  - Quality of Work Life: South Oakland., 1980-1982 (Box 58A, Folder 7)
  - Quality of Work Life: Publicity, Speeches, and News Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 58A, Folder 8)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 58A, Folder 9)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 10)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 11)
  - Quality of Work Life: Letter to Charles Brown, Chairman, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 12)
  - Quality of Work Life: Convention, Jul 3, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 13)
  - Quality of Work Life: Meeting in Chicago, IL, Jul 29, 1981-Jul 30, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 14)
  - Quality of Work Life: Seminar at Penn. State, Aug 10, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 15)
  - Quality of Work Life: Taping of Seminars, Piscataway, NJ, Aug 13, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life: Harvard University, Cambridge Mass., Jan 5, 1982-Jan 7, 1982 (Box 58A, Folder 17)
  - CWA/AT&T QWL Seminar: Morristown, NJ, May 26, 1982-May 27, 1982 (Box 58A, Folder 18)
  - CWA/AT&T QWL Seminar: Parsippany, NJ, Jun 14, 1982-Jun 15, 1982 (Box 58A, Folder 19)
  - Quality of Work Life: Harvard University, Jun 21, 1982-Jun 23, 1982 (Box 58A, Folder 20)
  - Quality of Work Life: Committee Meeting, Southwestern Bell and Dist. 6-Aug 2-3, 1982, undated (Box 58A, Folder 21)
  - Quality of Work Life: National Meeting, Dallas, Texas, Sep 21, 1982-Sep 22, 1982 (Box 58A, Folder 22)
  - Quality of Work Life: Publicity, Speeches, and News Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 58A, Folder 23)
  - Quality of Work Life: Joint Working Conditions Committee, 1982, 1987 (Box 58A, Folder 24)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 58A, Folder 25)
  - Quality of Work Life: Meeting, NY Telephone Co. Headquarters, Apr 25, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 26)
  - Quality of Work Life: Meeting at CWA headquarters, Apr 26, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 27)
  - Quality of Work Life: National Committee Meeting, Chicago, Ill., May 9, 1983-May 10, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 28)
  - Quality of Work Life: CWA/AT&T National Committee Meeting, Atlanta, GA, May 16, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 29)
  - Quality of Work Life: Conference, Airlie, VA, Sep 9, 1983-Sep 11, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 30)
  - Quality of Work Life: Final National Committee Meeting, Dec 5, 1983 (Box 58A, Folder 31)
  - Quality of Work Life: Union/Management National Council Meeting, Apr 17, 1984-Apr 18, 1984 (Box 58A, Folder 32)
  - Quality of Work Life: Council Meeting, Cancelled, 4/12/1985/ (Box 58A, Folder 33)
  - Quality of Work Life: Seminar, Hopewell, NJ, Cancelled, May 6, 1985-May 10, 1985 (Box 58A, Folder 34)
  - Quality of Work Life: National Council Meeting, Feb 28, 1986 (Box 58A, Folder 35)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Corr., 1987 (Box 58A, Folder 36)
  - Quality of Work Life: Semi- Autonomous Workgroups, 1987 (Box 58A, Folder 37)
  - Quality of Work Life: General Corr., 1988 (Box 58A, Folder 38)
  - Quality of Work Life: QWL Road Map, undated (Box 58A, Folder 39)
  - Project on Technology, Work, and Character: Participation, 1980 (Box 58A, Folder 40)
  - Joint Working Conditions and Service Quality Improvement Cttee, 1980-1981 (Box 58A, Folder 41)
  - Restructure of Bell System, 1981 (Box 58A, Folder 42)
  - Technology Change Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 58A, Folder 43)
- Series V: CWA Officers' Papers, 1939-1990
  This series includes the correspondence of union presidents Joseph A. Beirne and Glenn E. Watts documenting collective bargaining, government relations, community service, political action, and relations with the AFL-CIO and other international unions. Also included are speeches, Joseph A. Beirne's diaries, financial and legal records. This series documents both the internal operations of the CWA and its relationships with the labor, civil rights, and women's movements.
  - Subseries V:A: Beirne (Joseph A. Beirne), 1939-1980
    - J.A. Beirne, Diary (Dictated Daily), 1945-1946 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - J.A. Beirne, Diary (Dictated Daily), 1947 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - J.A. Beirne, Diary (Dictated Daily), 1948-1949 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Diaries: Joseph A. Beirne, 1939, 1942-1959 (Box 60)
    - Diaries: Joseph A. Beirne, 1960-1967 (Box 60/61)
    - Diaries: Joseph A. Beirne, 1968-1974 (Box 62)
    - General Correspondence: Joseph A. Beirne, Jan 16, 1949-May 1, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, Jun 2, 1949-Aug 29, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, Sep 1, 1950-Nov 2, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1961-1974 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - By-Laws; Divisions: Analysis & Approval, 1947-1949 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Executive Board Polls, 1947-1954 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Membership Cards: CWA, 1947-1969 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1948-1951 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Revocation of Division #42 Charter, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Division By-Laws, 1949-1950 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Division #35 (District 9): Local Elections, 1949-1950 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Independent Unions - Eastern Seaboard Alliance, 1949-1951 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Insurance Study: M. E. Segal; Report on Establishing Insurance Co., 1949-1956 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Congress of Women's Auxiliaries (Newsletters; Constitutions), 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - CWA: City Councils, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Wages and Working Practices Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Review of Selected CWA Staff Vouchers, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Military Leave Act: Department of the Army/Signal Corps, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Convention Correspondence; Notes, 1952-1954 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Executive Committee Meetings and Minutes, 1952, 19551966 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Contributions: FY 1953; Ex. Bd. Committee Appointments/Review (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Dissolution of Dist. 10 (Installation) and Dist. 11 (Sale), 1953-1954, 19501950 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Wage and Working Practices Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Local 3107: Election Appeal, 1954-1958 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Wage and Working Practices Committee, 1954-1959, 19661966 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Memoriam to C. W. Werkau: Sec-Treas (CWA Ex. Bd.), 1955 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Investigation of District 4 Elections/Dist. 4 Director, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1955-1959 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Report of Executive Board Comm. On Security Clearance, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - CWA Song; Correspondence, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Local 1150 Elections, 1958-1959 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Local Elections, 1958-1961 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Landrum-Griffin Correspondence, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Insurance, 1960, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - NLRB - Representation, Pacific North West Bell (Plant Eng.), 1961 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Appeals Files, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Local 9510: Local Trials; Bob Watson, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Labor Organization Bond: Local 6350 Welfare Fund, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Appeals, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Appeals - Home Sale and Purchase Plan - R. B. Porch / L. B. Daniel, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - Appeals - Local 4000 Mailing List, 1965, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - Corr. To Ex. Board (Union Accomplishments and Assessments), 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 43)
    - Recall of Charter, Local 1160 and Termination of Administrator, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Local 4000: Constitution Interpretation/Exhaustion of Internal Remedies, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - Local 4000: Responsibilities of Officers & Staff, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 46)
    - Local 4390: Elections, 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 47)
    - Martin E. Segal Co.: Employee Health Insurance Plans, 1966, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - Appeals: Arnold Sawatske Holiday Case: WI Tel. Co., 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 49)
    - Appeals: Local 1101: NY Plant Bargaining Unit Election, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 50)
    - Appeals: Norman Mackey: Ratification Procedures of 1952, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 51)
    - Appeals: Norman Mackey: Extension of Ratification (Role of Bargaining Comm.), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 52)
    - Appeals: Norman Mackey; Jurisdiction of Local 4000/N. M. Response, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 53)
    - District 6: St. Louis, MO, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 54)
    - District 8: Tucson, AZ, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 55)
    - Local 2323: Local By-Laws, Initiation Fees, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 57)
    - Staff Assignments, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 58)
    - Executive Board Polls, 1971, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 59)
    - Appeals: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 60)
    - CWA Women's Activities and Consumer Affairs, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 61)
    - Cataloging Assignment of J. A. Beirne's Records (by Ebba Muller), 1976-1977 (Box 63, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence - U.S. Presidents, 1946-1959 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - U.S. Presidents, (Assistants Cabinet Officers. Etc.), 1961-1964 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Presidential Corr. (Assistants, Cabinet Officers, Etc), 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - U.S. Presidents (Assistants, Cabinet Officers. Etc.), 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - U.S. Presidents, (Assistants, Cabinet Officers. Etc.), 1970-1974 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Matters - Earl Pippin (Appointment & Bio), 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Letters to Members (Correspondence with members), 1962-1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Letters to Members & Responses, [8/12]/1966 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Letters from Members Local 2551, Milwaukee, MN, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Letters to Members & Responses, [3/15]/1968 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Letters to Members & Responses, [5/1]/1968 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Letters to Members & Responses, [5/5]/1968 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Letters from Members: "Anti" Beirne, 1947-1971 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Mailing Lists to all Districts (Correspondence; Legislation), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Legislation, 1947-1969 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Legislation - Labor Laws for Ohio, 1965-1971 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Legislation, 1947-1969 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Government: State General Correspondence, 1947, 1959, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - State Legislation: Kane and Koons Opinions, Etc., 1947, 1949-1950 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - State Legislation: Disability Benefit Systems, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - State Legislation: 4.1 Labor Legislation, 1951-1954 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - State Legislation: Oregon, 1961-1968 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Situation In Oklahoma, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Legal: General (Correspondence - Legal), 1941-1949 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1945, 1947-1950, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - NLRB: Legal Correspondence; Joseph A. Beirne; NFTW, 1947-1950 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Legal: Approval Of Legal Counsel, 1951, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Legal: Attorney Resignation, Everett Cotter, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Legal: Correspondence General, 1947-1951 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Legal: Correspondence, Divisions1949-1953, undated (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Legal: Everett Cotter, Recommendation for Appointment to FCC, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Legal: Legal Opinions, 1943-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Attorney Henry Mayer, Activities, 1945-1955 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Attorney Henry Mayer, Activities, 1946-1954 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Attorney Henry Mayer, Activities, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Attorney Henry Mayer, Activities, 1958-1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Bills for Legal Service, Leon Consensus, Attorney, 1951-1952 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Legal: Southern Strike, US Court of Appeals, Transcript, 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Legal: R.C. Eckhardt, Attorney, Retainer Fee Authorization, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Legal: Legal Matters from 1955 Strike vs. Southern Bell, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Legal: Ruth Dennis, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Legal: T. Adair, Recommendations for NLRB Position, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Legal: T. Adair, Recommendations for NLRB Position, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Legal: Appointment Recommendations to Federal Positions, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Legal: Legal Counsel Retainer, Ontario, Canada, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Local 1180, Welfare Fund, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Services and Bills, Dist. 4(Correspondence; Regulated Industry), 1973 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Public Utilities Commissions' Rate Increase Applications; Corr., 1947, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Rate Cases, 1948-1949 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Rate Cases: Policy on Intervention, 1950-1959 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Rate Cases: State Rate Regulations, 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Rate Cases: Western Union, (FCC Docket #18270), 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Public Utilities Commissions, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Negotiations; Monitoring, CA Public Utilities, 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Negotiations; Monitoring, CA Public Utilities, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Public Utilities Commission: CA (Tel, Monitoring Equipment), 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Public Utilities Commission: CA (Tel, Monitoring Equipment), 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Negotiations; Monitoring, CA Public Utilities, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Negotiations; Monitoring, CA Public Utilities, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Monitoring, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - FCC: Transfer of AT&T Telegraph Facilities to Western Union, 1949-1953 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - FCC Investigation: Docket #16258, 1955, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - FCC Investigation: Docket #16258, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - FCC Investigation: Docket # 16258, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - FCC Investigation: Docket # 16258, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Federal Comms. Commission: Fairness Doctrine, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Western Union Wire Merger: FCC Docket # 18519, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Bargaining; Notes ( J.A.B); Corr., 1943-1955, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Beirne, Corr. Negotiations (Dist. 1) - Bell Labs, 1947-1960 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Negotiations ( Dist. 1) - New Jersey Tel co. DN #55, 1946-1951 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - NFTW-CWA Labor Management Relations: Bell System, 1948-1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Western Union Wire Merger, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - CWA Correspondence with AT&T & Bell Systems Officials, 1958-1967 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Replies From Bell System Presidents to J.A. Beirne Telegram, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Replies From Bell System Presidents to J.A. Berine Telegram, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - CWA Correspondence with AT&T and Bell Systems Officials, 1961-1971 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Labor Management Relations on Bargaining, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Labor Management Relations: Joseph A. Beirne Correspondence with Robert D. Lilley, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Meetings with Bell System Management, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Corr. With AT & T and Bell System Officials, 1972-1975, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - CWA Meetings with Bell System Executives, 1946-1959 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - AT & T: Employment Outlook in the Telephone Industry, 1947, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - NFTW: Labor Management Relations and Legislation before Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1947 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - NFTW: Labor Management Relations in the Bell System, 1950 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - AT & T Stock - Proxy Voting - Stockholder's Meeting, 1948-1955 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - At & T Employee Stock Purchase Plan - Revision of U-540 S.E.C., 1950, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - At & T Anti - Trust Suit, 1949, 1968, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Labor Management Relations & Bell System: Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Negotiations (Dist. 1): Irene J. Aley, 1963-1971 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - District 1 Negotiations: Local 1101 Ex. Bd. Meeting, 1965-1973 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - District 1 Negotiations: Local 1101 Officers' Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - District 1 Negotiations: NYC Govt.; Supreme Ct. Probation Officers, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - District 1 Negotiations: NYC Govt.; Adm. Employees; Municipal Mgmt Society (MMS), 1959-1965 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Negotiations: Adm. Employees & MMS, 1965-1966 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Negotiations: Adm. Employees & MMS, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Negotiations: Adm. Employees & MMS, 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Sample Union Contract, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Collective Bargaining Contract; Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Negotiations, District 1: ITT World Com., 1954-1956 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Negotiations, District 1: ITT World Com. Merger with Press Wireless, 1960-1970 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Negotiations, District 1: ITT World Com. Grievances Re: Merger, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Bell System: Reaction to Nicholas Johnson Speech, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - AT&T-CWA Filing with IRS in re Wage Stabilization, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Bell System: Senate Sub-Committee Investigation, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Cards and Lists, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Cards and Lists, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Cards and Lists, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Cards and Lists, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Cards and Lists, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Cards and Lists, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Cards and Lists, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Cards and Lists, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Cards and Lists, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Cards and Lists, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Cards and Lists, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Christmas Greetings; Union Newsletters & Papers, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Cards and Lists, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Cards and Lists, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Cards and Lists, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Cards and Lists, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Cards and Lists, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Christmas Cards and Lists, 1973, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Community Service Committee, 1945-1949 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Community Services Committee, 1945-1949 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Community Services Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Minutes: Community Service Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Community Service Committee, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Community Service Committee, 1948-1951 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Minutes: Community Service Committee, Mar 14, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Community Services Committee, Jan 1951-May 1951 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Community Services Committee, Jan 1951-May 1951 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Minutes: Community Services Committee, Jun 1952-Oct 1952 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Community Services Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Community Services Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Community Services Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Community Services Committee, Aug 1953, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Community Services Committee, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Minutes: Community Services Committee, ca.Apr 1953 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Minutes: Community Services Committee, ca.Apr 1953 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Community Service Committee, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence: Community Service Committee, ca.Mar 1953-Aug 1953 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Community Service Committee, ca.May 1953-Jul 1953 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Community Service Committee, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Community Service Committee: Community X Project, 1951-1959 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Community Service Committee: Community X Project, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: Community Service Committee's Community X Project, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Community Service Committee - Guide to Community Services, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Community Service Committee - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Community Service Committee - Other Materials, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Community Service Committee - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 4)